Finding Aid for College of Pharmacy (University of Michigan) records, 1864-2010
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Topical Files 1953-1992
  - 1917-2003
    - Correspondence
      - Julie Esther Emanuel 1917-1951 (Box 30)
    - Dean’s Advisory Committee 2000-2002 (Box 30)
    - Dean Ara G. Paul Retirement Celebration 1995
      - General (Box 30)
      - Tributes (Box 30)
    - Dean’s Brunch 1980-1991, 12 folders (Box 30)
    - Development Strategies, 2 folders (Box 30)
    - Distinguished Alumnus Award (Box 31)
      - 1976 (Box 31)
      - 1978 (Box 31)
      - 1979
        - General (Box 31)
        - Blackmer, T. Waldo (Box 31)
      - 1980
        - Correspondence (Box 31)
        - Jackson, Eugene L. (Box 31)
        - Lyons, Fred W. (Jr.) (Box 31)
        - Miller, Russell R. (Box 31)
        - Zografi, George D. (Box 31)
      - 1981
        - Correspondence (Box 31)
        - Benet, Leslie Z. (Box 31)
        - Bergstein, Stuart J. (Box 31)
        - Bright-Parker, Clavenda W. (Box 31)
        - Downing, Nedra (Box 31)
        - Superstine, Edward (Box 31)
        - Tousignaut, Dwight (Box 31)
        - Wiltse, John A. (Box 31)
        - Zienty, Ferdinand B. (Box 31)
      - 1982
        - Correspondence (Box 31)
        - Benet, Leslie Z. (Box 31)
        - Bush, Paul W. (Box 31)
        - Kelly, Paul N. (Box 31)
        - Osterberger, David J. (Box 31)
        - Pierpaoli, Paul G. (Box 31)
        - Vrabel, Rayburn B. (Box 31)
      - 1983
        - Correspondence (Box 31)
        - Guo-Jie (John) Liu (Box 31)
        - King Chiu Kwan (Box 31)
      - 1984
        - Correspondence (Box 31)
        - Kabat, Hugh F. (Box 31)
        - Parker, Paul (Box 31)
        - Pierpaoli, Paul G. (Box 31)
      - 1985
        - General (Box 31)
        - Committee (Box 31)
        - Church, Richard M. (Box 31)
        - Crampton, Thomas W. (Box 31)
        - Haithco, William (Sr.) (Box 31)
        - Kabat, Hugh F. (Box 31)
        - McLaughlin, Jerry Loren (Box 31)
        - Sytsma, Julia (Box 31)
        - Williams, Patricia Bell (Box 31)
      - 1986
        - General (Box 31)
        - Bowles, Mary L. (Box 31)
      - 1987
        - General (Box 31)
        - Walgreen, Charles R. III (Box 31)
      - 1988
        - General (Box 31)
        - Church, Richard M. (Box 31)
      - 1991 Lipper, Robert Allen (Box 31)
      - 1992
        - Barna, Rohdan (Box 31)
        - Haithco, William (Sr.) (Box 31)
        - Hirshfield, Joanne (Box 31)
      - 1993 Stewart, James Thomas (Box 31)
      - 1995
        - General (Box 31)
        - Abramowitz, Paul (Box 31)
        - Higby, Gregory James (Box 31)
      - 1996 Selection Criteria Changes (Box 31)
    - Emeritus Alumni Classes 1996-1998, 3 folders (Box 32)
    - Emeritus Club Reunions 1980-1988, 9 folders (Box 32)
    - Homecoming
      - 1987 (Box 32)
      - 1991 (Box 32)
      - 1995 (Box 32)
      - 1997 (Box 32)
      - 1998 (Box 32)
    - Prescott Circle Dinner 1991-1999, 9 folders (Box 32)
    - Program Description undated (Box 32)
    - “Proposal to Gustavus and Louise Pfeiffer Research Foundation to Develop and Implement a Life-long Learning Curriculum for Competent Clinical Practice in Pharmacy,” 1983 (Box 32)
    - Senior Class Night 1978-1979 (Box 32)
    - Steering Committee Meeting Materials 1976-1999, 25 folders (Box 32)
    - Whitney Award Winners List 1990 (Box 32)
- Executive Committee 1973-2001
  [RESTRICTED for thirty years from date of creation]
  The Executive Committee Series (1.5 linear feet, 1973-2001) documents the decision-making and program implementation processes of the College of Pharmacy. Materials include meeting minutes, constitutions, codes of conduct, policies on student records, program guidelines, curricular proposals and recommendations, and class and lecture descriptions. These records also include information on faculty performance and student conduct. As such, access to these files is restricted.
  - Executive Committee Minutes 1973-1998
    - Minutes 1973-1991, 4 folders (Box 16)
      [PR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2021 ]
    - September 23, 1991 (Box 23)
      [ER RESTRICTED until July 1, 2020 ]
    - October 14, 1991 (Box 23)
    - November 11, 1991 (Box 23)
    - November 25, 1991 (Box 23)
    - December 16, 1991 (Box 23)
    - January 13, 1992 (Box 24)
    - February 24, 1992 (Box 24)
    - March 9, 1992 (Box 24)
    - March 23, 1992 (Box 24)
    - March 30, 1992 (Box 24)
    - April 13, 1992 (Box 24)
    - April 27, 1992 (Box 24)
    - June 15, 1992 (Box 24)
    - June 22, 1992 (Box 24)
    - July 21, 1992 (Box 24)
    - October 20, 1992 (Box 24)
    - December 15, 1992 (Box 24)
    - January 22, 1993 (Box 24)
    - February 5, 1993 (Box 24)
    - March 16, 1993 (Box 24)
    - April 6, 1993 (Box 24)
    - April 20, 1993 (Box 24)
    - May 18, 1993 (Box 24)
    - June 15, 1993 (Box 24)
    - July 6, 1993 (Box 24)
    - August 2, 1993 (Box 24)
    - September 3, 1993 (Box 24)
    - October 1, 1993 (Box 24)
    - October 15, 1993 (Box 24)
    - November 2, 1993 (Box 24)
    - December 2, 1993 (Box 24)
    - January 12, 1994 (Box 24)
    - February 10, 1994 (Box 24)
    - February 18, 1994 (Box 24)
    - March 18, 1994 (Box 24)
    - April 1 1994 (Box 24)
    - May 6 1994 (Box 24)
    - June 17, 1994 (Box 24)
    - July 1, 1994 (Box 24)
    - October 7, 1994 (Box 24)
    - October 11, 1994 (Box 24)
    - November 18, 1994 (Box 24)
    - December 2, 1994 (Box 24)
    - January 13, 1995 (Box 27)
    - April 7, 1995 (Box 27)
    - May 12, 1995 (Box 27)
    - June 2, 1995 (Box 27)
    - June 16, 1995 (Box 27)
    - June 30, 1995 (Box 27)
    - July 21, 1995 (Box 27)
    - September 1, 1995 (Box 27)
    - November 10, 1995 (Box 27)
    - November 17, 1995 (Box 27)
    - December 15, 1995 (Box 27)
    - January 5, 1996 (Box 27)
    - January 15, 1996 (Box 27)
    - February 12, 1996 (Box 27)
    - April 5, 1996 (Box 27)
    - May 3, 1996 (Box 27)
    - June 7, 1996 (Box 27)
    - June 21, 1996 (Box 27)
    - August 2, 1996 (Box 27)
    - September 6, 1996 (Box 27)
    - October 4, 1996 (Box 27)
    - November 15, 1996 (Box 27)
    - January 10, 1997 (Box 27)
    - April 4, 1997 (Box 27)
    - May 2, 1997 (Box 27)
    - Box 27 (cont.) June 6, 1997 (Box 27)
    - August 29, 1997 (Box 27)
    - October 3, 1997 (Box 27)
    - December 5, 1997 (Box 27)
    - January 16, 1998 (Box 27)
    - March 20, 1998 (Box 27)
    - May 1, 1998 (Box 27)
    - June 8, 1998 (Box 27)
    - June 26, 1998 (Box 27)
    - July 13, 1998 (Box 27)
    - August 12, 1998 (Box 27)
  - Executive Committee Non-Meeting Approvals
    - July 1993-November 1993, 4 folders (Box 28)
    - January 1994-December 1994, 8 folders (Box 28)
    - February 1995-December 1995, 8 folders (Box 28)
    - March 1996-December 1996, 7 folders (Box 28)
    - January 1997-December 1997, 11 folders (Box 28)
    - January 1998-June 1998, 5 folders (Box 28)
    - July1998-December 1998 (Box 33)
    - January 1999-April 1999 (Box 33)
    - May 1999-June 1999 (Box 34)
    - July 1999-November 1999 (Box 34)
    - December 1999 (Box 34)
    - January 2000-June 2000 (Box 34)
    - July 2000-November 2000 (Box 34)
  - Meeting Materials (Box 33)
    - January 20, 1999 (Box 33)
    - March 19, 1999 (Box 33)
    - June 3, 1999 (Box 33)
    - July 23, 1999 (Box 33)
    - August 20, 1999 (Box 33)
    - September 16, 1999 (Box 33)
    - October 21, 1999 (Box 33)
    - December 17, 1999 (Box 33)
    - January 25, 2000 (Box 33)
    - February 18, 2000 (Box 33)
    - April 11, 2000 (Box 33)
    - June 2, 2000 (Box 33)
    - July 5, 2000 (Box 33)
    - September 1, 2000 (Box 33)
    - September 29, 2000 (Box 33)
    - November 22, 2000 (Box 33)
    - December 13, 2000 (Box 33)
    - January 10, 2001 (Box 33)
    - January 26, 2001 (Box 33)
  - Committee Files
    - 1983-1990, 16 folders (Box 16)
      [PR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2020 ]
    - 1991-1992, 4 folders (Box 17)
  - Ad Hoc Faculty Committee on Discipline 1990 (Box 17)
    [RESTRICTED until 2065 ]
  - Executive Committee Elections 1980-1990 (Box 17)
- Adjunct and Clinical Appointments
  The series Adjunct and Clinical Faculty Appointments contains position postings, searches and personnel files for various adjunct faculty and clinical track faculty positions in the period 1989-1994. Positions include pharmacokinetics, chief drug officer, pharmacy practice, and various clinical pharmacist positions. Due to the presence of personnel information, access to these files is restricted in accordance with the Personnel Records restriction.
  - 1989-1994
    [PR RESTRICTED until July 1 2034 ]
    - 1989-1994 (Box 35)
    - 1989-1994 (Box 36)
      (continued)
    - 1989-1994 (Box 37)
- Archived Website
  The Archived Website series (20.6 MB, 2002- 2006; 2010-[ONGOING]) comprises the content of the College of Pharmacy's public website designed to disseminate information to prospective and current students, faculty and staff, and the general public. This series documents the academic programs, accomplishments, resources, events, and people at the College of Pharmacy. Content includes important news and announcements, publications (such as faculty newsletters and course catalogs), and information about admissions, curriculum, degree requirements, faculty, and the overall mission of the College. The series is arranged chronologically and includes content captured by the Internet Archive starting in 1996 as well as captures provided by Bentley Library archivists in 2002, 2003, and 2006. Starting in 2010, this archived website and related resources has been captured on a regular, ongoing basis as part of the University of Michigan Web Archives, hosted at http://webarchives.cdlib.org/a/universityofmichigan/.
  - College of Pharmacy 1996-2008
    - 1996-2008
      (These versions were preserved by the Internet Archive and are made available through its Wayback Machine. The Bentley Historical Library is not involved in the collection or maintenance of this material.)
    - May 15, 2002, .ZIP file
    - May 22, 2003, .ZIP file
    - May 6, 2006, .ZIP file
  - Archived College of Pharmacy home page 2010-[ongoing]
  - Archived websites related to the College of Pharmacy 2010-[ongoing]